medicalvibe.com 2009-09-30

# Privacy Policy

**MedicalVibe**  

---  
  
**Effective Date 4/20/2008**  
  
**Privacy Policy**

MedicalVibe’s privacy policy aims to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using MedicalVibe, located at www.medicalvibe.com, or any related pages which can be accessed from our site. 

By using or accessing MedicalVibe, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.   
  
**Information Collected**

When you register and visit MedicalVibe you provide the Company with two types of information: personal information you intentionally choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site. 

When you register with MedicalVibe, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal, professional or preference information that you provide to us. 

When you enter MedicalVibe, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all site visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to us. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

When you use MedicalVibe, you may form contacts, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. 

By using our site, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.  
  
**Use of Information Obtained by MedicalVibe**

When you register with MedicalVibe, you can create your own profile. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the MedicalVibe network. We will use your email address to send you notifications regarding new email messages or comments to your profile and any new services offered by MedicalVibe that we think you may find valuable. 

Profile information is used by MedicalVibe primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others.  
  
**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**

We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you.  
  
**Links** and **Third Party Advertising**

MedicalVibe will contain links to other websites and third party advertising. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites or the advertising. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.   
  
This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by MedicalVibe and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers or linked websites.  
  
**Invitations and Communication to Non-Members**

MedicalVibe members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. MedicalVibe does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, and invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from MedicalVibe may contact us to request the removal of their information from our database.  
  
**Changing or Removing Information**

Access and control over most personal information on MedicalVibe is readily available through the profile editing tools. Our users may modify or remove any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their account may do so by contacting the administrators at _[admin@medicalvibe.com](mailto:admin@medicalvibe.com)_. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to site members.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on MedicalVibe, however, (e.g., Forums) you generally cannot remove such communications.  
  
**Security**

MedicalVibe takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of our site, please contact us at _[admin@medicalvibe.com](mailto:admin@medicalvibe.com)_.  
  
**Terms of Use, Notifications and Revisions**

If you choose to visit, register and participate in MedicalVibe your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of, and application of law of the state of Florida. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Notice of new policies and their effective date will be posted on the web site in advance of the effective date. It is your responsibility to regularly review our Terms of Use. If you object to our policies, please do not use our site and remove yourself as a member.
